import { Question } from "../App";

export const rnmData: Question[] =
    [
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Rick's portal gun invention?",
            "options": ["Portal Gun", "Time Gun", "Dimension Blaster", "Wormhole Device"],
            "answer": "Portal Gun"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Rick's catchphrase?",
            "options": ["Wubba Lubba Dub Dub!", "Oh Geez!", "Pickle Rick!", "Get Schwifty!"],
            "answer": "Wubba Lubba Dub Dub!"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which dimension is the main Rick and Morty from?",
            "options": ["C-137", "J-19", "K-42", "Z-99"],
            "answer": "C-137"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Rick's daughter?",
            "options": ["Beth", "Summer", "Jessica", "Tammy"],
            "answer": "Beth"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is Morty's crush at school?",
            "options": ["Jessica", "Summer", "Tammy", "Beth"],
            "answer": "Jessica"
        },
        {
            "question": "What does Rick turn himself into in a popular episode?",
            "options": ["A pickle", "A robot", "A cat", "A cucumber"],
            "answer": "A pickle"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Morty's sister?",
            "options": ["Summer", "Jessica", "Beth", "Tammy"],
            "answer": "Summer"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is Birdperson's arch-enemy?",
            "options": ["Phoenixperson", "Evil Morty", "Tammy", "Mr. Nimbus"],
            "answer": "Phoenixperson"
        },
        {
            "question": "What does Mr. Meeseeks help people do?",
            "options": ["Solve problems", "Fix portals", "Rule dimensions", "Cook meals"],
            "answer": "Solve problems"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the theme park inside a homeless man created by Rick?",
            "options": ["Anatomy Park", "Funland", "Microverse", "Dino World"],
            "answer": "Anatomy Park"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the President of the Citadel of Ricks?",
            "options": ["Evil Morty", "Rick C-137", "Rick Prime", "Birdperson"],
            "answer": "Evil Morty"
        }
    ];